(
"ai_sub_version": "2.9.1",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 7,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 15,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch"
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 5,
"max": 5,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
In a kingdom far far away where all Nyut-Nyut lives,
a sudden calamity strikes among the Nyut-Nyut who lives in harmony.
A pink giant monster has emerged out of nowhere and created havoc everywhere.
A lot of buildings and villages were destroyed.
All Nyut-Nyut were left hopeless
until a mysterious magical squirrel arrived to find a legendary weapon, the Nut Blade.
The legend said that this mysterious squirrel will bring an end to this calamity...
強くなれる理由を知った
I learned the reason why I can be strong
僕を連れて進め
Take me with you and move forward
Yeah!
泥だらけの走馬灯に酔う
I'm intoxicated by the mud-covered lantern slides
こわばる心...
This stubborn heart...
震える手は掴みたいものがある それだけさ
and trembling hands, there is something I want to grab, that's all
夜の匂いに... (I'll spend all thirty days and nights)
Even if I glare at the night sky... (I'll spend all thirty days and nights)
空睨んでも... (staring into the sky)
staring into the sky...
変わっていけるのは自分自身だけ
the only thing I can change is myself,
それだけさ
that's all
強くなれる理由を知った
I've learned the reason I can become stronger
僕を連れて進め
Take me with you, move forward
どうしたって! 消せない夢も
Even with dreams that can never be erased no matter what
止まれない今も
Even in this present moment that I cannot stop
誰かのために強くなれるなら
If I can become stronger for the sake of someone
ありがとう 悲しみよ
Thank you, sorrow
世界に打ちのめされて負ける意味を知った
Beaten down by the world, I learned the meaning of losing
紅蓮の華よ咲き誇れ!
Bloom proudly, crimson lotus!
運命を照らして
Light up my fate
イナビカリの雑音が耳を刺す
The noise of lightning pierces my ears
戸惑う心...
My confused heart...
優しいだけじゃ守れないものがある? わかってるけど
Is not enough just by being gentle, are there things I cannot protect? I know, but...
水面下で絡まる善悪
Good and evil tangled below the surface
透けて見える偽善に天罰
Divine punishment for the transparent hypocrisy
(tell me why, tell me why, tell me why, tell me, I don't need you)
逸材の花より 挑み続け咲いた一輪が美しい
It is more beautiful to be the one single flower that kept challenging and bloomed, than a talented flower
乱暴に敷き詰められたトゲだらけの道も
Even the road covered in thorns, violently spread
本気の僕だけに現れるから
It only appears to the real me
乗り越えてみせるよ
So I will show I can overcome it
簡単に片付けられた守れなかった夢も
Even the dreams that were easily put away and could not be protected
紅蓮の心臓に根を生やし
Taking root in the crimson heart
この血に宿ってる
Residing in this blood
人知れず儚い 散りゆく結末
Secretly and fleetingly, the ending of scattering
無情に破れた 悲鳴の風吹く
Ruthlessly broken, the wind of screams blows
誰かの笑う影 誰かの泣き声
Someone's laughing shadow, someone's crying voice
誰もが幸せを願ってる
Everyone is wishing for happiness
どうしたって! 消せない夢も...
Even with dreams that can never be erased no matter what...
止まれない今も...
Even in this present moment that I cannot stop...
誰かのために強くなれるなら...
If I can become stronger for the sake of someone...
ありがとう 悲しみよ
Thank you, sorrow
世界に打ちのめされて負ける意味を知った
Beaten down by the world, I learned the meaning of losing
紅蓮の華よ咲き誇れ!
Bloom proudly, crimson lotus!
運命を照らして...
Light up my fate...
運命を照らして
Light up my fate
Oh no! Everything is burned down! My house and the entire village is destroyed!
What is going on? Are you alright?
A giant monster... burned down my entire village with its fire breath.
That is bad! Do you know where that monster is heading?
I think it's headed to the next village.
Don't worry. I shall take care of it for you so it won't destroy the other village too!
In order to do that, I need to collect power by singing and music.
So please, lend me your power, oh dear villager!
Oh! I will!
星を廻せ 世界のまんなかで
Go around the stars, right in the middle of the world
くしゃみすれば どこかの森で蝶が乱舞
When you sneeze, butterflies flutter wildly in a forest somewhere
君が守る ドアのかぎ デタラメ
The key to the door you protect is unreliable
恥ずかしい物語
An embarrassing story...
舐め合っても ライオンは強い
Even if we lick each other's wounds, the lion is strong
生き残りたい
I want to survive
まだ生きていたくなる
I feel like I still want to live
星座の導きでいま、見つめ合った
By the guidance of the constellations, we gazed at each other just now
生き残りたい
I want to survive
途方にくれて キラリ枯れてゆく
Becoming lost at what to do, wither away in a sparkle
本気の身体 見せつけるまで
Until I show off my serious self,
私眠らない
I won't sleep
風はやがて 東へ向かうだろう
The wind will head toward the east before long, right?
高気圧 この星の氷河を襲う
The high atmospheric pressure attacks this planet's glaciers
さそい水を飲んだ 胸がつらい
My chest that drank the priming water feels painful
遠まきな物語
A story that surrounds me from afar
かじり合う 骨の奥まで
Biting into each other, deep into our bones
生き残りたい
I want to survive
まだ生きていたくなる
I feel like I still want to live
星座の導きでいま、見つめ合った
By the guidance of the constellations, we gazed at each other just now
生き残りたい
I want to survive
途方にくれて キラリ枯れてゆく
Becoming lost at what to do, wither away in a sparkle
本気の身体 見せつけるまで
Until I show off my serious self,
私眠らない
I won't sleep
We're shouting to survive
何しに生まれたの
What was I born to do?
何しにここにいる
What am I here to do?
生き残りたい
I want to survive
埋まらない傷 光恐れてた
My unburied wound feared the light
許された生命がいま、引かれ合った
Our permitted lives attracted each other just now
さまよい果てて
My wandering is over
君のとなりで ほてり鎮めたい
And next to you, I want to quell my blushing
本気の身体 見せつけるまで
Until I show off my serious self,
私眠らない
I won't sleep
生き残りたい
I want to survive
がけっぷちでいい 君を愛してる
I'm fine with being on the edge of a cliff, I love you
目覚めたい生命がいま、惹かれ合った
Our feelings of wishing to wake up attracted each other just now
狂気に代えて
Replacing it with madness,
祈り捧ぐよ 君を愛してる
I offer a prayer, I love you
星座の導きで...
By the guidance of the constellations...
生き残りたい
I want to survive
まだ生きてたい 君を愛してる
I still want to live, I love you
本気のココロ 見せつけるまで
Until I show off my serious heart,
私眠らない
I won't sleep
星が降る
[Song: Stars are Falling]
羽根もない
Even without wings,
この私が
I,
憧れてた
who longed...
あの空
...for that sky,
背伸びして
stretched on my tiptoes,
星を掴む
to grab a star...
真似をして
...imitating...
みた
...and tried to do so.
負けないで
Don't give up,
願いさえも
even when the darkness...
飲み込む闇
...swallows up your wishes.
それでも
Even so,
手探りで
groping in the dark,
夢の欠片
I will go...
集めに行くのよ
...to gather the fragments of my dreams.
ただグルグル回る
Just spinning around and around...
車輪の中で
...inside this wheel.
走っても走っても
No matter how much I run,
辿り着けなくて
I can never reach my destination.
先を行く君の
I only ever stared...
背中ばかりを見ていた
...at your back as you forged ahead.
いつか超えられる
One day, I will surpass you.
もっと強くなりたい
I want to become much stronger.
ただひとり
All alone,
生まれてきた
born into this world,
その記憶も
with even those memories...
失くして
...completely lost.
泣き声も
Even if I lament...
届かないと
...that my cries...
嘆いてみても
...won't reach, I can still believe.
信じていい
I want to believe,
大きな樹に
these claw marks...
しがみついた
...left from clinging...
爪痕
...to that great tree...
あの空へ
...are proof...
近づこうと
...that I am trying...
している証s
...to reach that sky.
風が雲を
As the wind...
流して
...sweeps the clouds away...
あぁ
Ah...
星が降る
...the stars are falling.
羽根もない
Even without wings,
この私が
I,
憧れてた
who longed...
あの空
...for that sky,
背伸びして
stretched on my tiptoes,
星を掴む
to grab a star...
真似をして
...imitating...
みた
...and tried to do so.
負けないで
Don't give up,
願いさえも
even when the darkness...
飲み込む闇
...swallows up your wishes.
それでも
Even so,
手探りで
groping in the dark,
夢の欠片
I will go...
集めに行くのよ
...to gather the fragments of my dreams.
Ugh, I think after all this singing,
my power is still not enough to defeat the giant pink monster!
I heard you, young warrior.
I can help you with your worry.
As I, the keeper of the legendary weapon Nut Blade, will lend you its power.
Is this the voice of the Fire Blade Priestess?
Yes, you are right. I will lend you the power of this Nut Blade if you can prove yourself that you have the spirit to fight the pink giant monster.
Hah! Okay!
Dragon One!
胸に刻めよ 時代のリーダー
Carve it into your chest, leader of the era
見た目よりかは かなり Clever
Rather cleverer than you look
渇いた心 荒むよりは
Rather than letting your dry heart wither
時に泣いてみれば 見えてくる
If you cry sometimes, you'll see
明日かけるのは 紛れもなく新しい自分
The future you run toward is unmistakably your new self
誰かのためでもなく ただもっと上を目指せ
Not for anyone else's sake, just aim even higher
Dragon Screamer!
昇る竜のようだ
Like a rising dragon
金の光が 呼んだ未来が 導くんだ 僕らを
The future called by the golden light will guide us
Dragon Screamer! Dragon Fever! No Question!
Dragon One!
満ちているのに はるかなゴールは
Even though it's within reach, the far-off goal
見た目よりかは かなりに Harder
Is actually harder than it looks
君が踏み出す 勇気持てば
If you have the courage to take a step forward
やがて開く道が 目指すべき
The path will eventually open up to where you should aim
場所選ぶのは 紛れもなく新しい自分
Choosing the place is unmistakably your new self
翼を手にした君は どないな山も越える
You, who have obtained wings, will cross any mountain
Dragon Screamer!
叫ぶ竜のようだ
Like a screaming dragon
銀の嵐が 吹き飛ばすんだ 迷いとか 恐れを
The silver storm will blow away your hesitation and fear
Dragon Screamer! Dragon Fever! No Question!
Oh my way 走り出せ 駆け抜けるライバルという風
Oh my way, start running! The wind called 'rivals' rushing past
それなら conquest ハイペース 輝く未来未だ見ぬ明日
In that case, conquer at a high pace, aim for the shining future and what is yet to be seen
あきらめず探し続け ついに不変の夢 forever victory
Never giving up, keep searching, finally, an unchanging dream forever victory
宙に浮かぶドラゴン 背に浴びる光 世界をその手に
A dragon floating in the sky, light shining on its back, the world in your hands
Dragon Screamer!
昇る竜のようだ
Like a rising dragon
金の光が 呼んだ未来が 導くんだ 僕らを
The future called by the golden light will guide us
Dragon Screamer! Dragon Fever! No Question!
Dragon Screamer!
叫ぶ竜のようだ
Like a screaming dragon
銀の嵐が 吹き飛ばすんだ 迷いとか 恐れを
The silver storm will blow away your hesitation and fear
Dragon Screamer! Dragon Fever! No Question!
You have proven me your spirit. I shall bestow upon you the Nut Blade.
Thank you. I shall use this weapon to defeat the monster.
Now I have the Nut Blade, I shall continue my journey to defeat the giant pink monster.
If my hunch was right, I think...
I should go through the forest next.
Oh no! What happened to you, almighty dragon?
ピンクの巨獣にやられた。今は力が入らん。
I was defeated by the pink behemoth. I have no strength right now.
巣も破壊されてしまった。
My nest has also been destroyed.
Oh no, that is bad! I can help you recover if you can take me straight to the giant monster in exchange.
任せておけ。
Leave it to me.
[おおかみは赤ずきんに恋をした]
[Song: The Wolf is in Love with Little Red Riding Hood]
偶然からはじまる 必然の一場面（ワンシーン）
An inevitable scene that begins from a coincidence...
遠くに見えたのは 逃げる赤色
What I saw in the distance was a fleeing red color.
不思議な森 of 奥で 見つけた黒い影と
With a black shadow found in the depths of a mysterious forest...
何かが始まる予感、怖くて逃げ出した
I had a premonition that something would begin, and ran away, scared.
「出会い」は終わりに 続くシナリオ
The "meeting" is a scenario that leads to the end...
だからわざと 遠回りをした
So I intentionally took the long way around.
会いたい、なんて 触れたい、なんて 話したい、なんて 思わない
I'd never think of wanting to meet, wanting to touch, or wanting to talk...
かよわい君と 狡い僕が 「出会う」其れが終わりさ
With you, who is weak, and me, who is cunning, "meeting" is the end.
残酷だって罵ったって 運命は変わらない
Even if I curse that it's cruel, fate won't change.
ああ どうして、君が？ どうして、僕が？ おおかみと赤ずきんなんだ
Ah, why you? Why me? It's the wolf and Red Riding Hood.
きっと君は今日も この道を訪れる
I'm sure you'll visit this road again today.
そして僕は今日も ずっと 見守るしかできない
And I can only watch over you again today.
君はあの木の先で いつも通り隠れてる
You're hiding past that tree as usual.
私は気づかない ふりしたまま通り過ぎた
I passed by, pretending not to notice.
視線は交わさない 声は交わさない
Our eyes don't meet, our voices don't cross.
ため息だけが虚しく重なる
Only our sighs emptily overlap.
逢えなくたって 触れなくたって 話せなくたって いいから
Even if we can't meet, touch, or speak, it's fine.
頼りない君と ぎこちない僕が そこに居るだけでいいんだ
As long as the helpless you and the awkward me are just there, that's enough.
これが恋だって言わないなら 言葉なんて無くていい
If you won't call this love, we don't need any words.
考えたって 考えたって エンディングは変わらない
No matter how much I think, the ending won't change.
会いたいかったんだ 触れたかったんだ 話したかった、本当は
I wanted to see you, I wanted to touch you, I wanted to talk to you, in truth...
かわいい君と 優しい僕が 出会い結ばれるエンド
An ending where the cute you and the kind me meet and are united.
何回だって 何回だって 神様に願ったよ
Over and over again, I prayed to God.
でも 悲しいくらい 悲しいくらい おおかみと赤ずきんなんだ
But sadly, so sadly, we are the wolf and Red Riding Hood.
泣いてる君を 慰めたくて 伸ばした腕が震える
Wanting to comfort you crying, my outstretched arms tremble.
愛しているよ 抱きしめたいよ だけど、できないんだよ！
I love you, I want to hold you close, but I can't do it!
どう足がいたって どう願ったって 爪も牙も消えない
No matter how I struggle or wish, my claws and fangs won't disappear.
だからただ待ってるよ 君の涙が止むまで あの木の先で
So I will just wait, until your tears stop, past that tree...
ずっと...
Forever...
おーーー！
Ooooh...!
Ah, here we go! If you eat this, you can recover super quick!
感謝する。よし、完全回復だ。
My thanks. Alright, I'm fully recovered.
今すぐ怪獣の元へ案内しよう。
Let me guide you to the monster right away.
Okay, let's go!
とべ FLY HIGH!!
Fly, FLY HIGH!!
ひかる翼で
With glowing wings,
いま全部全部おき去って
now leaving everything, everything behind,
To be fly...
高く fly
Fly high,
最果ての未来へ
To the furthest future.
傷だらけの若鳥が
A young bird covered in wounds
空を睨んでる
is staring at the sky.
低空飛行する奴らが
Even if those flying at low altitudes
笑おうと海の果てが見たい
laugh at me, I want to see the edge of the ocean.
心を無にして向かい風に乗り
Empty your heart, ride the headwind,
助走をつけて
gain speed,
ホップ、ステップ、ジャンプで境内へ
with a hop, step, and a jump!
To be fly high, high, high!
汗と血と涙で
With sweat, blood, and tears,
光る翼が
the glowing wings
君をどこへだって連れて行く
will take you anywhere.
青い衝動と
Baring your blue impulse and
本能と爪牙を剥き出しにして_
instinct, with fangs bared,
患難の旅路も
even on this difficult journey,
夢叶うまで
until the dream comes true,
何度だって to be fly
no matter how many times, to be fly,
高く fly
fly high,
最果ての未来へ
to the furthest future.
ぽつり降り出した雨が_
The rain that suddenly started to fall
翼狂わせる
makes my wings falter.
行く手には黒い雲_
Black clouds lie ahead,
今長い嵐の夜が来る
now, a long stormy night is coming.
轟く雷鳴と砕ける波涛を
The roaring thunder and breaking waves..._
喝采にして
turn them into applause,
アン、ドゥ、トロワで
with a one, two, three!
To be fly high, high, high!_
いつも胸の奥を焦がす炎が
The flame that always burns deep in my chest
道を照らしだす灯台になる
becomes a lighthouse that lights the way.
夜明け前の光芒が
Because the beams of light before dawn
才能の花咲かすから_
will make the flower of talent bloom,
命尽きるまで
until my life ends,
限界を超え最高速で
exceeding limits at maximum speed,
To be fly..._
Ah...
Ah..._
To be fly high, high, high!_
汗と血と涙で_
With sweat, blood, and tears,
光る翼が_
the glowing wings
君をどこへだって連れて行く_
will take you anywhere.
青い衝動と_
Baring your blue impulse and
本能と爪牙を剥き出しにして_
instinct, with fangs bared,
全部全部おき去って_
leaving everything, everything behind,
To be fly high!!_
いつも胸の奥を焦がす炎が_
The flame that always burns deep in my chest_
...love me too
Utara ku kecil dahulu
My northern star, small in the past
The love will last, it will
Selamanya 'ku kan peduli, right?
Forever, will you care, right?
To me, broken thing have I become
To me, a broken thing have I become
And you see, life is pain
Truly I had enough
Ordinary day it seems
An ordinary day, it seems
The clouds of love in the sky
Painted colors in my paradise
Titik hujan menyegarkan segala
Raindrops refreshing everything
Bunga-bunga emosi manusia
The flowers of human emotion
Mekar dan berkembang megah selamanya
Blooming and growing grandly forever
Ah!
Will I love you like you love me too
Utara mu lebih dahulu
My northern star, more in the past
The love will last, it will
Selamanya 'ku kan ada di sini
Forever, I will be here
To me, enchanting have I become
And you see life is fair
Truly I am enough
Ordinary day it seems
An ordinary day, it seems
The cloud of lies in the sky
Painted color in my paradise
Titik hujan menghapuskan segala
Raindrops erasing everything
Luka, duka emosi manusia
Wounds, sorrows of human emotion
Rapuh dan terjatuh, lelah di dunia
Fragile and fallen, tired in this world
The halo lingers on my ego
Blinding light that radiates
Evaporates the sad in me
A soundless whisper
Follow me, never let go
Bahagia jadi nyata
Happiness becomes real
Berdua
Together
To me, obsessive have I become
And you see life is fair
Never I had enough
Never have I had enough
Ordinary I will be
The cloud and the color of rainbow
The cloud and the color of the rainbow
Start to show in my paradise
Titik hujan meleburkan segala
Raindrops dissolving everything
Luka, duka emosi manusia
Wounds, sorrows of human emotion
Rapuh dan terlalu lelah di dunia
Fragile and too tired in this world
Hi, finally I can see you
Awan gelap yang membentuk aku
The dark clouds that form me
Titik hujan membasuh
Raindrops washing
Bunga-bunga perasaan
The flowers of feelings
Dan melebur satu warna yang bermakna
And melting into one meaningful color
Stop right there!
I'm here to stop you and release all the Nut-Nuts from misery!
わぁ！あの巨大なモンスターを倒したなんて信じられない！
Wow! I can't believe that we've defeated the giant monster!
実はこんなに可愛いんだね！あぁん！
It's actually this cute! Aw!
お祝いに、もう一曲歌っちゃおう！
As a celebration, let's sing one more song!
ひらひら葉の雫
Fluttering drops on the leaves...
弱気な毛並み抱いて
cradling my timid fur,
叫んだ空
I screamed at the sky.
神様気取りの丸い眼球が 世界を愛して壊し終えました
The round eyes playing God loved the world and finished destroying it.
誰のもの 誰のもの 我のもの 邪魔ものは排除した
Whose is it? Whose is it? It's mine. I eliminated the obstacles.
監督がなんとか言ってたって エゴに捕まれて拒めないんだ
No matter what the director said, I'm caught in my ego and can't refuse.
まるで足りない 物足りない 死にたくない
Completely insufficient, unsatisfying, I don't want to die.
機械仕掛けの狂った声で 踊ってみせよう
I'll show you how I dance with a mechanical, crazed voice.
うんざりだよ シンドローム 愛してるわ
I'm sick of it, this syndrome, I love you.
もう やめてよ
Please, stop it already.
殺しても 脳波買ってきて 売れば幸せですか
Even if you kill, if you buy brainwaves and sell them, are you happy?
作られたショーケース もがき出したい基盤
The fabricated showcase, the foundation I want to struggle out of...
世界 虚ろの果て
the world, at the end of emptiness.
魂を一体どこに隠した
Where on earth did you hide your soul?
観葉植物よ 雨粒求め
Oh, foliage plants, seeking raindrops,
歌と舞う
singing and dancing
ヒバリの空
in the skylark's sky.
輪廻転生 機械論 進化論
Reincarnation, mechanism, evolution...
人が人でなく 人でなくなるときに 堅牢に請う こらえろ
When people stop being human, beg the fortress and endure it.
歌だけは未来へ届くよ
Only songs will reach the future.
空から空へと繋げるよ
They will connect from sky to sky.
限りなく泣く光 ヒバリたちを残す
Endlessly crying lights, leaving behind the skylarks.
大砲を聞かせてくれたっけ
Did you let me hear the cannon fire?
メリディアン 二人のこと愛してる
Meridian, I love the two of them.
嘘でもいいから一度だけでも聴かせてよ
Even if it's a lie, let me hear it just once.
どこで会って どこで笑ってました？
Where did we meet, and where did we laugh?
今は幸せですか
Are you happy now?
置き去りのまま届かない思いごめん
I'm sorry for the unreachable feelings left behind.
なんで言えなかったのかな
Why couldn't I say it?
悲しい思い出は果てに隠した
I hid my sad memories at the end.
歌よ あなたの元へ
Oh song, go to you...
雨粒求め
seeking raindrops,
時を舞う
dancing in time...
ヒバリの空
in the skylark's sky.
一人でも笑っていけるんだ
I can keep smiling even alone.
一人では生きていけないんだ
I cannot live alone.
ずっと拒んだり 愛したり
Constantly refusing, constantly loving...
野良猫は捨てられる姿で生きていける
Stray cats can live even in their abandoned state.
殺しても 脳波買ってきて売れば幸せですか
Even if you kill, if you buy brainwaves and sell them, are you happy?
作られたショーケース
The fabricated showcase...
もう逃げ出せない痛い未来 行き先の鍵
A painful future from which there is no escape, the key to the destination.
魂を一体どこに隠した
Where on earth did you hide your soul?
観葉植物よ 雨粒求め 歌と舞う
Oh, foliage plants, seeking raindrops, singing and dancing...
夜明けを告げたら
once the dawn is announced...
ヒバリの空
the skylark's sky.
うー！はい！
Ooh! Yes!
Hi everyone! Woo!
Now, now, now...
How was my performance?
Did you like it?
Did you guys have fun?
And also...
for celebrating my victory...
and of my birthday...
we have special merch! Yes!
So, here is the merch! Woohoo!
Woah! How cool is it?
And it's not only cool...
this year's merch was designed to be useful too, so...
let's have a closer look, shall we?
First up...
Ooh! Woah! Hahaha!
It's an awesome A3 tapestry drawn by netural-sensei! Woah!
The whole illustration just...
Woah, it looks super awesome! It looks so cool!
You can see that I'm holding my beloved...
Just look at that warrior Risu with full dark side! Isn't that awesome?
Woo! Don't miss it!
And also don't forget you guys got to buy it, at least five, okay?
And I think, let's see what we have next.
Woo, a super cute tumbler for everybody!
So you guys won't forget to hydrate, um...
You can use it to drink water, and...
you can use it pretty much always, so be sure to use it every day, okay?
And next, we have this!
Woah, a squirrel smartphone ring?
Ooh, so you can be super comfortable and remember me...
when you're holding your phone.
And it also will secure your phone in your hand.
Very, very convenient!
And I think, let's see the full set now! Woo!
Woah, there's so much stuff, actually!
And also, don't forget we have the full set purchase bonus here!
Yeah!
So I will explain it a little bit...
For those of you who purchase the full set...
will also receive a signed, foil-stamped postcard!
And for my super Risuners who purchase...
the limited edition full set...
will receive a postcard autographed by none other than me!
Autographed by me! Isn't it awesome? Woah!
And the pre-order window is only a month, so...
make sure that you don't miss it!
Oh, oh, oh, also, one more thing!
Did you guys listen...
to my new original song, 'Hoshi ga Furu'?
It will be officially released...
after this stream at midnight JST...
JST, okay? On my YouTube channel!
So go listen to it! And...
maybe who knows that later we will have MV for it?
I don't know!
And last but not least, for all of you who joined...
my membership...
you don't want to miss a special additional 3D performance in membership...
just right after this show has ended!
If you haven't joined my membership yet...
do not hesitate, because the extra show...
is going to be mind-boggling!
What are you waiting for? Join membership...
now! Woohoo!
Ooh! Woohoohoo!
Oops, um, but I think the time is up, aww...
But yes, I have to continue with the membership show now!
So thank you so much everyone for your support...
for this whole six years, especially!
And thank you for celebrating my birthday together with me! So...
Bye-bye! Otsurisu!
The Rise of the Nut Warrior